RUN BY A FLEET OF AI AGENTS.
AND YOU CAN'T SEE, STEER, OR GROW THEM.
AGENTS ARE BLACK BOXES.
ORG CHARTS ARE FROZEN.
SO WE BUILT THE OPPOSITE.
NOT A DASHBOARD — A COMPANY YOU WALK INTO.
OMO MISSION CONTROL
A company you walk into.
BUILT ON ADK · GEMINI · MCP
REASON WITH GEMINI · ORCHESTRATE ON ADK · CONNECT OVER MCP
ANY SYSTEM. ONE PROTOCOL.
ADS · PAYMENTS · SUPPORT · YOUR INBOX
SPEAK A GOAL.
TO YOUR CHIEF OF STAFF
IT DELEGATES TO SPECIALISTS.
PULL LIVE DATA · ACT ON REAL SYSTEMS
EVERY DECISION, UNFOLDING LIVE.
THE COMPANY GROWS ITSELF.
WHEN THE MISSION NEEDS MORE
A BUILDING RISES.
AN AGENT WALKS IN · A DASHBOARD RENDERS TO LIVE DATA
NO ENGINEER. NO DEPLOY.
JUST SAY IT.
OBSERVABILITY IS WHERE YOU STAND.
EXTENSIBILITY IS EVERYTHING YOU SAY
NOTHING SHIPS WITHOUT YOUR ONE TAP.
NOT A TOOL FOR RUNNING AGENTS.
IT'S WHERE THEY LIVE, WORK, AND MULTIPLY
OMO MISSION CONTROL
The operating system for the autonomous company.